Now, let's see, inserting not at any position.
So we have in C.
We need to create our.
Method called Insert after it took in the parameters, this truck node reference bravest note and end
new date.
OK.
First of all, a check if the given previous nod is not afraid, not equal, equal to null, then print
after given previous not cannot be null director.
Because if we are returning, if we are checking, if they're not the link, at least.
Previously equal or equal to null and pointing to null, so we are inserting at the end so our empty
linked list or a linked list that it is a reference to previously not equal, equal to none.
And this is not acceptable.
Allocate new none, so we are going to insert after we specify in Ont. and we are going to insert after
this note, then you know, we create struck note reference, new note and Malloch size of struck.
No, we create this new not struct and put in the data new node data equal to new data.
I am just getting the new note data equal to new not binding and referencing the new not now make the
next of new note as next of previous.
Not by specifying Newton new node next equal to previous node of next reference.
So I am just copying the reference and splitting it and reversing the reference move their next of the
previous node as new.
Not so Priv.
Not next equal to new.
Not.
OK.
Let's see how this works.
We have three nodes.
The first 1866 and one one nine.
These are the data of the nodes, and the reference of the hat is to the middle, in the middle, to
the last and the last reference to the null.
Now we need to insert.
After the middle and you nod here, cold, it was two to 200 and this 200, this method or this note
were referenced to the last.
So please pay attention while we are copying and changing that reference.
So we have moved the last.
And we have inserted a new nod after the middle.
And then you nod now should the reference to the last.
Not OK, so.
The reference of the medal would be equal to four thousand twenty four and the reference of the new
not that there's insert that would be a reference to the thirty three thousand and forty.
This is very important to trick.
OK, guys.
So.
And certainly not at any position is done in Java by making the same concept of C, but I'm changing
some basic syntax, so check if they're given not as null.
Checking if previous, not equal to none.
Then print that given previous nod, it cannot be known.
And the second step is allocate the note and put that data inside it.
Not new, not equal.
New, not and past the new date and for make next.
Often new, not as next of previous.
Not that we have switched their address, the address and the references of the notes.
And last step is make next of previous.
Not as you know, this is time.
Complexity would be equal to all of one because I am directly executing this method to the.
At the known position, known not.